let nutritionQuiz = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Fatty fish is a good source of what nutrient?",
    answer:
      "Omega-3s.Fatty fish such as salmon, sardines, halibut, and black cod provide omega-3 fats, which may reduce the risk of cardiovascular disease and other disorders.  It's best to get your omega-3s from fish rather than supplements; recent studies show diminshed absorption from omega-3 pills as compared to fish.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "True/False: Multigrain breads are always whole-grain.",
    answer:
      "False. The term 'multigrain' means only that more than one grain is present. The primary ingredient is usually refined wheat flour. Whole-grain flour contains the bran and the germ, and so is rich in vitamins, minerals, and fiber. Refining wheat removes nutrients, and even when it's 'enriched', only some are added back. A true whole-grain bread lists only whole grains in the ingredients, not 'wheat' or 'enriched wheat', which is simply refined (white) flour.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "Which food is highest in potassium - a medium banana or one cup of yogurt?",
    answer:
      "Yogurt. While bananas are an excellent source of potassium, with 420 milligrams, many other foods have even more! Yogurt has 530 mg/cup, orange juice has 500mg/cup, and broccoli has 460mg/cup. Also rich in potassium are tomatoes, apricots, spinach, beets, prune juice, potatoes, lentils, soybeans, nuts, and sunflower seeds. A potassium-rich diet helps control blood pressure. The goal is 4,700 mg per day.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Which of the following foods contain calcium - figs, almonds, soybeans, or collard greens?",
    answer:
      "All of the above! Dairy foods are the best sources of calcium. Milk has 300 milligrams per cup and yogurt has even more. But some plant foods provide calcium too, particularly soybeans (175-260 mg/cup) and leafy greens (150-250 mg/cup, cooked).",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "Which of the following foods contains no cholesterol - roast turkey, olive oil, grilled chicken, or bacon?",
    answer:
      "Olive oil. Dietary cholesterol is only found in animal products. Fruits, vegetables, grains and all other plant-based foods are entirely free of cholesterol.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "True/False: A label that lists trans fats at 'zero' means that the food contains no trans fat.",
    answer:
      "False. Because of the way labeling regulations are worded, a 'trans-fat free' food may still contain small amounts of partially hydrogenated oil (<0.5g per serving). These trace amounts can add up, especially since standard serving sizes are often small.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Which fast food item has more sodium - McDonald's large fries, a Burger King veggie burger, or a Dunkin' Donuts corn muffin?",
    answer:
      "It's the veggie burger! Most fast food is very high in sodium â€” even items you might think are not. The veggie burger has 900 mg, followed by the corn muffin at 770 mg. The fries come in a distant third at 290 mg.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "How much fiber should you aim for every day?",
    answer:
      " 21-35 grams.  A cup of bran cereal with a banana (10 grams), a cup of broccoli (6 grams), a pear (5 grams), a sweet potato with skin (5 grams), and a slice of whole-wheat bread (2 grams) get you within that range.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "What is the acronym for the 'good' cholesterol - LDL, VLDL, or HDL?",
    answer:
      " HDL. High-density lipoprotein, aka HDL, is the molecule your body uses to absorb bad cholesterol and return it to the liver so it can be flushed from the body, keeping it from collecting on the linings of your arteries. Higher levels of HDL can reduce your risk for heart disease and stroke.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "Which of the following foods does not contain fiber - broccoli, oatmeal, steak, or baked beans?",
    answer:
      "Steak. Fiber, which improves blood sugar control, lowers cholesterol, and helps prevent constipation, is found only in plant foods.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "Vitamin D is found in which of the following foods: eggs, milk, or mushrooms?",
    answer:
      "All of the above! Milk is fortified with vitamin D and is the major dietary source, with 100 IU per cup. Small amounts of vitamin D are also present in fatty fish, egg yolks and mushrooms. Orange juice, soy milk, margarine, yogurt, and breakfast cereal may also be fortified. But to get the 800 to 1,000 IU a day we recommend, vitamin D supplements are usually necessary, since it's difficult to get this much from food.",
  },
];
